Heat. Hey, Heat.
>> [music]
>> H hello everyone. Wait wait wait wait.
Oh the thing is not showing up. What?
Oh no. Okay, there you go. Hello
everyone.
Good evening to all.
Hello. Hello. How's everyone doing
tonight?
Today. Yeah, tonight. Tonight. Today.
Everything is the same. But yeah, how
are you guys doing? Hello. Hello.
So um
m
So today we are going to be playing Ark
Raiders. Yep. The same game I've been
playing and enjoying recently. I will be
also doing that today as well.
Yes. Yes.
Um
give me a minute. Uh it seems to me like
the chat is not showing up.
Um
let me double check that. What is
happening?
Um give me a minute.
Give me a minute.
But yeah.
Hi.
So,
what is this?
Oh, I'm getting issues. I'm having
issues. No,
I'm having issues today. Oh, no.
Oh, no. No. No. No. Let me just uh
quickly
fix this. Uh I did not notice this until
now.
Uh this is weird.
A bit awkward, isn't it? Um
Yep, it is a bit awkward. One second.
Um,
okay. Let me just run it and we should
be fine. Yeah, my PC is not handling and
liking this game at all. At all, man.
I can honestly say that
cuz this game no doesn't like
um my my my PC is not liking this game.
Yeah, it's probably that.
Oh, yeah. How has everyone been? It's
Christmas now.
It's Christmas season coming in.
Uh
uh
bro, the moment I uh not look at my PC,
the stuff breaks. I hate this.
The moment I do not look at stuff,
everything breaks. Like none there.
This is so weird.
Super weird.
Give me a minute. I'm trying my best to
fix this.
Uh
technical difficulties are such a pain.
Honestly,
it is such a pain. Honestly, uh
things not work the way you want it to
be. Things not go
and yeah, things go
in.
Uh, I wanted to man,
why you not working anyway? Let's switch
to the game.
Very good.
Hi. Uh,
one second.
I don't need that. So, uh, expedition
has come. If you didn't know, expedition
came and many of the early players, day
one players have been
um
have who have done the expedition have
reset it. Meanwhile, me I have done till
page three of the second expiration
stuff. Yeah. Yeah. I um
have done up to three. We need a little
bit of sensors.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to get my 5
million before February. That's in 60
days. So 60 days, but from today, that's
like February 23rd
or something. Uh
yeah.
Wait, hold up.
Does February have? Hold up. Hold up.
Yeah, February 23rd. Yeah. Sorry, I
forgot. There's no leap here today. It's
[music] next year. Yeah. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Um,
so there's that. And
give me a minute.
Give me a minute.
Do let me know when my YouTube stream
does not work or load. Okay. So I can
quickly
quickly shiftly um fix it.
So that it works.
So
all right, let's go.
We finished the uh flickering flames
event.
which is nice to see.
And I got these ones as well.
Um, I have maxed out my scrappy to level
five. Got everything. We just need to
level up our Yeah, almost all the
benches are level two now. I just need
to get them up to level three and we are
good.
Yeah. So, let's go. Uh, and also there's
trials this time. I want to get the
trial stuff done, actually. So, let's do
the trials tonight.
Oh, uh, spaceport has lush bloom. Okay,
let's do the spaceport. Yeah. Yeah,
we're going to do this.
If there's a lush boom event, I want to
do this.
Hope the audio is not too loud and
stuff.
If let me know.
Okay.
Let's go.
One second. Okay.
And there's another J.
All right, we're here.
>> Celeste here. Just a gentle reminder to
keep an eye out for those salvage sites
for TN. It may be just what we need to
get her to pull her weight.
>> So, during the lush bloom event or the
uh other events, I might get blueprints,
which is nice
though. I do not need the things.
Where's fire?
Oh my god.
You know what? Energy saving thingy.
I'll take this.
We'll recharge the thing using the arc
itself.
It's not much here, isn't it?
It's just your ordinary.
It's just your
ordinary
jock. You're getting sand in your butt.
[laughter]
Wow. Hello. Uh, Kixa.
Okay, I'm going to get this.
Yeah, I will be getting sand on my
place. Oh, this
bridge is this.
Okay.
Even though a lush bloom event is going
on, I do not know where to find
like
I actually don't know where to find the
baskets.
Oh, wait. There should be one inside of
this, right?
Technical is coming. There should It's
not here. Never mind.
>> I see a raider.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Oh, basket. basket. Yeah.
There's this.
We going to bridge this.
>> That's not Oh, there's a raider.
A raider over there.
>> Space boy.
Hey
All right.
Where did he go? Where did he go?
Oh my god.
>> Thanks, Raider.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, Raider.
There is no Oh. Oh. Oh. I need the the
server. We need uh sensors, right?
Yeah. Each of these server like thingy,
they will have at least one sensor.
And I will take that
cuz I need them
fuse grenades. Oh,
what I going to make? Uh, I have to uh
submit these for the expedition.
Second expedition.
Oh, lockers, lockers.
Let's find something good probably.
Handheld radio.
I going to
go.
Oh,
is that a weapon cage over there? Oh,
that is
weapon cage.
What do I get? A beret
brleta.
It's really dark over here now.
Really dark.
Ice cream scooper. Nope.
Spring cushion.
Interesting.
Well, the good stuff.
Oh, we got to bridge this.
Not much stuff.
Is it up? up.
Tuna can. I need the tuna can. I think
I'll rock this.
Take that up here.
Oh, that board. Uh,
think I can do that.
Oh my god, there's so many. Look. Uh,
thank you too much.
60k loot. Nice.
Also, you forgot something. Jock. Next.
Heal up.
Porttery. Okay. What is pottery?
I am running out of space.
Get this. What do we have here? Nothing.
The kiki sound.
Oh no.
Okay.
Oh, there's a bridge over here.
Also, we need the sensor for making the
uh raider hatch key. So, it's kind of
important either ways.
So, we can extract from here.
Oh, nice. Nice. That's a weapon cage.
What do we get here? A gun.
Okay, I'm going to put that there.
Ah,
music of um maybe this
Holy God, it's scary.
What is life? What is happening?
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, we eventually would have to
kill the reaper a leaper
someday. So there's that.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Hello
Is there someone below me?
I think there is someone below me.
There is someone below me.
Okay.
Toaster.
Should I take the toaster? I have like
so many.
I'm taking the toaster.
I've like checked all these places,
right?
Yeah, we can go.
68,000
worth of stuff.
>> Hey, hello.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
What is this?
Oh boy.
Anything left for me? Nothing.
This the person before me looted every
single thing.
Interesting.
They left a lot of
fabrical things.
Yeah, they left a lot of fabric things.
Uh, where did I find uh
medic bag again? Here. No,
I'll take this.
Okay. So, we could run to the X.
We could run to the extract.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Oh, someone died.
Okay, stand by for elevator.
>> Hey,
someone.
Bro, this guy had so many good stuff.
I
>> I got the instrument, by the way. I got
the instrument.
>> The poor guy died to someone. Maya, we
got an instrument.
We got a shaker.
My first instrument in the game.
Thank you. Oh my god. I got instrument.
I want to get the guitar, man. I want to
get the
get the guitar.
67k.
Crazy.
Hm.
Don't
um
I would say we did get a few bunch of uh
what do you call it?
Yeah, we did get a few bunch of this
thing.
A lot of loot initially.
Nice.
It's 31. Nice. That's a good This was a
good raid.
Some three
311.
No. Three 311 comma 0 023
0 032
uh money.
Okay. B city has lush bloom
increase amount of or we can do nitrate
though. Nitrate will be nice to do.
Oh, cold snap is also nice. You can do
the raiderish,
right?
Yeah, we could do the raiderish stuff
and finish it off.
Let me think. One second.
Give me a minute. And uh
Okay, give me a minute. Uh no, I need to
just end this.
What the heck?
Wait, where is this thing? I can't exit
it.
Wait, my PC is so
I'm choosing
weird today.
Uh,
why do I have Microsoft Edge?
What?
What is happening?
What the [sighs]
What?
Bro, this code I have to uh today's
stream is it's okay. I'll worry about it
later. Uh what other
shaker bar?
Okay, let's do the whole snap event.
We have to
do a lot of uh
gathering plans, right? Yeah.
do the command to.
Okay, let's go.
I honestly do not know where I'm going.
>> Hope you're close for the season,
Raider. It's a good day for picking
candleberries, but do beware of
frostbite.
[groaning]
Okay, we'll do this.
I feel like I need a map for this.
I honestly
uh
I can't find any lush bloom.
groceries. I can't find anything.
The textures aren't loaded in. Hello,
Solar. Welcome to the stream.
Uh textures aren't loaded in.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Oh, candle light.
We'll do this. Remember me? Yes, I do
remember you. Hello. It's been a while.
Hope you're doing well.
Okay, I'm taking damage.
>> [panting]
>> I'm taking damage
because I'm broken. Oh. Oh, no. It's
okay.
It happens. No worries.
No worries. No worries.
know one second.
Give me a minute. I'll just
do something
real quick.
How are you doing? I'm doing great. How
are you, Solar? It's been a while, huh?
Hope you're doing well.
Okay,
this should do it.
Okay, I fixed the bug I was having.
That landed over there. So, we'll go
this way.
I'm doing well. Glad to hear that. Nice.
Nice.
Oh, is this a Oh, it's a raider hatch
key.
Typing on phone is so annoying. It's a
car.
it. I think it's because you're not used
to it
perhaps.
Okay. I think it did not see me.
Yeah, it did not see me.
Oh my god. Okay,
that is so lucky.
I needed that. I got a magnetic
accelerator. Oh my god.
Lucky
still remember the old enough to.
Yeah. [laughter]
So that
my stuff. [laughter]
There's no
There is no
A moderator made the clip. A moderator.
Which one?
Ah, I think ah it was harsh or I think
my ex moderators. Yep.
Yeah. Kronos. Yep.
Oh, coffee.
Yes. Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas to
you as well.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, this is full looted.
Wow,
my legs. O.
Oh, you dead. Oh, okay. My Discord isn't
that active,
but yeah,
I mean it's good if you join for getting
notified and stuff, but yeah,
there is that.
I I was like
I haven't verified that. It's okay. No
worries.
Honestly speaking, I was like
considering to like
uh not keep a discover
crown thingy. What crown thingy? What
crown?
our crown.
Oh lord, I just headbutted that. Oh my
god.
Number plate.
I'm getting cold.
>> Let's go to the domes.
>> So, we go there and then extract. Maybe
a
>> Oh, YouTube has a laser board system.
That's why
YouTube has a crown uh thingy
for viewers and stuff.
It's similar to Twitches.
Uh
yeah, as soon as this twitches,
the the more you chat, the more you get
it.
Yeah.
That's how it works. The more you try,
the more you get it.
Okay. Nothing good here.
I might die.
Oh no, someone's already been here.
They collected all the plants now.
Wait, this is a late raid. I have to get
home. Oh my god, this is a late raid.
Why am I here?
Oh my god. Just extract the jock next.
Just extract. Don't stay.
Oh my god, that's a rocketeer.
That's a rocketeer. That's a rocketeer.
Okay. He didn't see me.
>> Okay. Extract.
>> This is security.
>> Am I the last guy?
So together
I haven't asleep since 900 p.m. Oh no.
Go sleep if you're feeling sleepy.
Do sleep to take care of your health.
Okay.
Make me
>> [laughter]
>> No, I can't force you to go to sleep.
>> It's up to you. Actually,
>> elevator.
Let's go.
Glad I didn't use that healing thingy.
All right,
let's see.
We didn't do much, but we leveled up.
That's good.
I I need a
The thing is not I I don't want to open
my browser and like um
I don't want to open the browser and
like make the stream lag.
So, we'll do night trade and we'll do
uh
Yeah, I'll do a night.
Don't keep talking to me.
found the nature.
>> Yeah, we can do another
Okay, the final thing I need humidifier.
Where will I get it? Residential. Okay.
10 components. Two magnet. Okay. I have
that leaper. How am I going to get this?
Did the stream just lagged? What
happened to the stream? Not don't tell
me the stream died.
Okay, stream is here. Yeah, if my stream
does do right now, I'll just fix it.
Oh, I can submit this.
stream going. Okay, good, good, good,
good.
I need to find
Wait, wait. I think I can buy this.
I think I can buy this one.
>> Got something for me?
>> Someone?
>> No. Ah, this it just reset it, didn't
it? What game are you playing? We are
playing the game called Arc Raiders as
an extraction shooter. PB.
>> We rely on growite
game.
>> Power outage can wreak havoc on our food
supply.
>> Arc Raiders. It's like an extraction
shooter.
Okay, let's go. Night raid.
We are going to do night raid and we're
going to do the trials where we'll do
uh either we do
husk thing first wave husk. We'll have
to do 20 or night. I got 20 or 10 of
them.
I have game recommendations. Yeah, sure.
You can suggest games. It depends if I
will play it or not because my PC is a
bit of a bottleneck.
Yeah.
And I recently bought this game, so I
would love it if you could search free
games instead.
green.
>> Okay, let's go.
Made someone just Okay.
>> Have your eyes adjusted to the dark yet?
Raider
>> Roblox? I'm tired of Roblox. I don't
want to play Roblox.
>> Suppliers say that Ark is twice as
vigilant after sunset.
>> Roblox. I had it. I installed that
after a while.
I got a bridge.
>> Hello Yuki. How are you? I'm doing
great. How are you?
Merry,
merry uh early Christmas wishes.
Merry early Christmas wishes.
I'm good and are you celebrating? Uh
that's tomorrow 24th.
Yeah, probably with family.
I mean, it's just a normal day to be
honest for me.
There isn't much.
Did someone open this? No.
mobile game. I can't play mobile games.
How will I play mobile games?
No, no, no, no.
Bad landing.
That was a bad landing.
Uh,
block blast. What type of game is it?
Ah, humidifier. Thank you. Okay, safe.
Okay, we will keep that.
We'll keep that. Nothing here.
Get this.
Oh, thank you for the hydrate reminder.
Let me bring some of this. Thank you. Oh
my god.
Oh, these set silver set. Nice.
I think this is looted.
Yep, these are loaded.
Oh [\h__\h]
I forgot. I forgot. I forgot.
I forgot about this guy's existence.
And I thought it was the moonlight. Cuz
it's night. Nah. But no.
I I thought that guy was going to kill
me, but thankfully no.
Oh,
we need this guy.
I don't have a grenade now.
Is he coming to me?
Yes. Got it.
[cough]
Why is there lights over here?
Also, we need to leave soon.
>> I see a player over there.
What is he doing?
I could leave from there.
An Ark Orbiter is on the road. The safe
window is closing. You have 10 minutes
to return to Sparanza. I repeat, 10
minutes.
>> Where is the rod? Ah, someone looted
this.
Slowly,
slowly, slowly.
Oh, this is not looted.
Lightning rod. Please, please, please,
please, please, please. Ah,
where will I get my lightning rod?
Please, please, please, please.
I heard if you
you get random blueprints
when you're doing events like this like
night raid and stuff. Not sure if it's
true though.
Oh, I needed that. Thank you very much.
Apparently, the game has been giving me
like sending me too late. Oh, weapon
cage.
Ah, nice. Thank you very much.
Oh, I needed that. I need that. Thank
you.
That's risky. Don't go.
Okay. It did not see me.
What is this room?
Wow, everything is looted.
Nothing for me, huh?
Also, we need to head to the extract.
to go to extract.
Oh, no one did this.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Don't shoot.
Oh [\h__\h]
I can use that.
Jump. Go.
>> Don't shoot.
All raiders, we have Ark on screen. 5
minutes left. Go find a way home. I
repeat, 5 minutes.
>> Oh god.
>> Leave. Leave. Leave. Leave.
Take every single thing. I'll just sell
it.
>> Hey. Hello.
>> Hello, Raider.
Oh my god, that scared me.
Oh my god. Nice.
Ah, thankfully I'm only getting friendly
people.
Which is nice.
That is really nice.
Huh? I think I'll go this way. Then the
movement,
right?
What do you think? They are not bad.
Those two are needed. Ah, mosquito.
Okay.
I didn't shoot much in this raid,
which is interesting.
Medium ammo.
Okay, one more night.
Go, go, go, go.
I got the [\h__\h] down.
Oh, yeah. I forgot to announce on
Discord that I'm live. So, I'll just do
that right now, I think.
Oh my god. My bad.
>> Apollo, here. Did you bring those
grenades, Raider? My new designs look
great on paper, but I don't need someone
to chuck them at some machines to know
anything for sure.
What?
Somebody looted this. Wow.
Okay, we'll go to M
about
>> let's go to the grandioso apartments.
How do you get inside this place?
Oh, this way.
Please don't be looted. Please don't be
looted. [laughter]
Why is the game giving me play?
It's why it's fully swept clean.
Nothing is left for me.
Insane.
I will not die here.
I need fabric.
What is this empty place?
Bro, even this place is a full is
looted.
They didn't keep anything for me. Huh?
Nothing at all. Huh?
Let's go to Plaza Rosa.
I guess Can I drop?
Get me. Get me. Get me.
Oh my god. I thought I got shot or
something.
Nice loot.
Well, let's try from here.
>> Uh, so
Lightning roar there.
Someone's killing the rocketeer.
Oh [\h__\h]
Oh my lord. Holy Mary, mother of God.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Nope.
Give me something. Give me something.
Yes. Thank you.
>> Did it die?
So, did the rocketeer die or
>> don't shoot?
>> Don't shoot.
Oh god, this stuff is also wipe to
clean.
Oh, I forgot the window was open.
Oh my holy god. What the heck?
That's why there were so many
mosquitoes.
>> An Arc Orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing. 10 minutes to get out
of there. I repeat, 10 minutes.
>> Oh my god, there were so many
mosquitoes.
Okay.
Oh [\h__\h]
Oh, that's the Easter egg.
Is there any other player?
Oh no.
People are extracting. Should I extract?
This is a bad raid.
>> Don't shoot.
Train control.
Okay.
People are traumatized by this game. I
think they're like,
uh, I want to get into the PVP part of
this game, man.
I wonder. And I mean, right now, I'm
peacefully looting and getting back
home. Now,
if I was aggressive,
oh Lord, I would be crying right now.
Oh my god.
Okay,
we need to repair this guy.
I can sell the hair. We're going to give
that
Not much of profit though.
Okay.
Okay. I want to kill the leaper.
Let me get some explosives.
Crude explosives, huh?
Gas grenade.
Small radius. Okay.
These mosquitoes so annoying.
Got quick fuse. This
uh
heavy fuse
one pack. Why not?
Three lure grenades. Yep. What? Wait,
what is this
secret grenade? Yeah.
We are not
>> uh this extra this.
We going to fight the matriarch. Okay.
I don't need to, but I just want to.
You feel me?
Why not? I'll just take everything
dark. much.
Um,
this should be enough. And we need to
take a lot of gunpowder.
I'll switch it with the I don't have the
renegade blueprint though.
That's the thing. Don't have the
renegade blueprint.
choke.
Okay, I'm going full, kid. I'm getting
full. I'm going hard this time.
Let's hope and pray we do not die.
Okay, we'll keep a def over here.
Uh if we have any teammates who are
dying in the battlefield now, we can get
them.
Uh
I think I have enough stuff.
Yeah.
Uh, I think so. I'm ready.
Uh, why do I feel like I'm missing
something?
>> Yeah, this guy.
I'm fully kided. I might need a Yeah,
[laughter]
I'm fully kided, [gasps] bro. Oh. Oh,
god. Okay,
this is going to be nice.
Watch me. No, no, no. Don't jinx it, Jo.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Do
not jinx it.
I did not jinx it.
So, we go to the matriarch.
Please give me a fresh raid.
Please give me a fresh raid. If it's not
a fresh raid, I will just uh uh not
surrender, just extract, but not
looting. We're just going to
we'll just be going to go battle the
matriarch this time solo. Not solo. Uh
if there are other players
fighting it, fresh rate, please, please,
please, please, please, please. It's a
fresh rate.
Watch your backs, raiders. The matriarch
has been spotted near your location.
Keep your wits about you if you decide
to go anywhere near and always keep a
close eye on her children.
I have to be extra careful. Oh,
heat.
Where would the matria be?
I had to leave my friend to backpack.
Hi, welcome back. No worries. No
worries.
I hear fighting.
Oh boy. I hear it.
I do hear it.
It's over there.
>> The water facility.
Make it in time. Make it in time.
Okay, it's uh over here this side.
>> Let's go to that location.
>> Hello, Dia. Welcome.
Welcome. Welcome.
Someone's extracting
Where is it?
There. Where is the matria
brother? What?
Where is the matria?
Uh
Bro, there's nothing.
>> Okay, I'm resetting.
I'm resetting.
So you see that guy,
that guy got the big boy guns, the epic
rarity guns, like literal r uh energy
guns.
Those are the the these people already
reached mid mid end game. Not end game,
mid game or something.
I'm still in greens. I'm still in
greens. I need to get to purple.
Okay, we'll do another one.
If there's ad on YouTube just watch on
kick. No, you can watch on other
platforms like kick and stuff if you
wish.
owner of the dam.
Someone died in front of me.
Oh, there you are.
there.
>> But not much people are fighting the
matriarch though.
>> Then what's the point?
>> Head home at the water treatment
elevator.
No one is fighting this.
a matriarch there.
Okay, I'm resetting again.
Okay, we are going to fight.
Let off.
They're not giving me a fight.
Stand by.
>> I It just saw me.
>> Terminal online.
>> Bye-bye.
I couldn't shoot it. That's fine.
Okay, next one.
Oh, the
know what? Let's do the reaper. That
matrix seems like a big hard difficulty.
I'm going to do the
I'm going to actually do the leaper.
Yeah, let's do the leaper then. I need
the corn now.
Ruined the homestead. Okay, let's go.
We rent our homestead.
Okay,
we take cover. Get inside a building if
needed. Throw as much as grenades as
much as possible. We get the core
extract.
Let's go to the ruined homestead.
>> That's the plan. Okay,
>> this is Apollo. Gate still standing.
Raider, you'll find the unfinished
structures scattered around the valley.
Look for construction signs and cones.
My previous crew came under heavy fire
before they could finish up.
I have to be careful. I don't want to
get caught by any patrol
patrolling art.
Okay, some people are fighting.
Oh, it's the it's the it's the it's the
Uh, let me get on top of the roof.
>> Don't shoot.
Okay. 3 2 1 Get ready jocknicks.
Holy
[screaming]
[groaning]
mother Mary.
Oh my god.
[groaning]
>> [groaning]
>> Okay.
Wow.
[groaning] Okay.
Heat. Heat.
N it.
>> [groaning]
>> Oh my god. Holy m
Oh my god.
Hello.
Hello. Hello. How you doing? It's been a
while.
I need people.
I can extract right from here. I have to
go with this much.
>> Go back.
Where is it?
Hey, don't shoot.
>> Oh my god, he's attacking another
raider.
>> Hello, Raider.
>> Hello there.
>> All right, focus on me. Is it stupid?
What? Oh my god.
Dumb dumb dumb dumb move. Thanks.
Oh [\h__\h] Run, run, run, run, run. That's
That's bad. That's bad. That's bad.
Okay,
bro. [\h__\h]
[groaning]
how?
How,
bro?
I brought 17 grenades.
Why?
Somebody help me. Please help. Help.
Help. Help.
Help.
[groaning]
Want to team up?
>> Team up. Don't shoot. Hello, Raider.
Hey. Hello Raider. Hello Raider.
>> Hello BT. Thank you for the Balto.
Balito. Thank you for the follow.
>> Hello Raider.
Hey. Hello.
>> Oh come in.
Want to team up? Hello Raider. Hey. Hey.
Team up. Want to go together?
Bro, no one's here.
Yeah, you got banned. You're a bot.
Apparently, I missed the whole arc.
Yeah, you did.
>> Hey, team up.
>> Help. I died. Take my loot.
>> [sighs]
[laughter]
>> I I at least have my wolf back, man.
Bro, I lost so much,
bro.
Why?
Uh, is it just me or did I hear curse? I
did curse. It's fine.
Um,
I don't need to be always family
friendly all the time, so it's fine.
I lost everything, bro.
I brought so many grenades. I brought so
many lure grenades. Everything going in
there.
What should I do now?
I got to go Stella free load out.
All
right, let's go.
Oh boy.
Let's try not to get PvPed.
Want to team up? Negative. Hey, don't
shoot.
Okay.
Oh my god. Nice
showstopper.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Somebody already looted all of this.
Oh, so this is a full looted area.
H. I did not mean to do that.
>> Don't shoot.
Okay, we can get the circuit from here.
Uh we need uh one advanced component.
And we should be good.
>> Hey, don't shoot. Okay.
Oh my god. Nice. Oh,
I got a elephant. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Okay,
we need to extract, bro.
Oh my god. We need to extract right now.
Oh my god. We got an Alf blueprint. We
got a Alion blueprint.
Isn't this the best OP
golden tiered sniper?
Okay, we need to extract ASAP.
I'm coming to Stella, man. Stella has a
lot of good stuff.
I can't reach there. I have to go.
Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Come on.
That's a dead body.
Let's use that metro entrance.
Holy [\h__\h]
I'm dead. I'm dead.
Oh, yeah. I'm dead. I'm going to go. Oh,
yeah. Yeah. Take care. Take care. Take
care. Take care. Solar. Thank you for
dropping by.
Uh below me.
>> Don't shoot.
>> [groaning]
>> What do you mean?
open. Stand by for train.
I am a wall. I am a wall. I am nothing.
I am nothing. I'm nobody.
Don't shoot.
>> Shredder in there.
>> Train has arrived. Watch the doors.
Stand by.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
The shredder. I hate the shredder, man.
Wait. 1 2 3 4 5 6 seven people were
there. Crazy. But yeah, this is a good
thing. We got
Aphilion blueprint.
That is nice.
Hold
up.
Wait. S for 5k.
Show stop her.
rest of the things we can.
Are you able to see my chats? I am able
to see your chat. Yes. Hello. Hello.
Welcome to the stream, Sophia Blade one.
>> Prohibited
sector.
We need the magnets.
Okay.
All right. Um,
paper is fragile.
>> One second.
Yeah, my PC is lagging.
Uh,
I have to use of my keys as well.
I want a loot bag on Stella actually,
but I'll take free load out just in
case. You never know what can happen.
Especially the stupid shredder is a
maniac.
That thing is pain.
Okay, let's go.
Don't shoot. Other
one's here.
Rocket thruster.
Is everything loaded?
Oh, it is.
Everyone swiped it clean. Wow.
Hey, don't shoot.
Oh, I can breathe inside. That's
nothing.
>> Don't shoot.
Heat. Heat.
appreciate it.
>> Oh my god, he gave me a blueprint.
The act of kindness is nice.
Heat. Heat.
What is happening?
>> Let's head home at the loading bay
metro.
Let's take that metro entrance.
Oh, brother.
I need the arc recharger.
Hey, don't shoot.
Someone died.
Oh, no. Don't leave me.
Don't shoot.
>> Don't leave me.
I'll extract with the blueprint friend
actually.
Uh
Your trained.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Okay.
Nice.
Oh, we finished the quest. That is nice.
We finished the quest. That is really
nice.
Have you been to Stella Mont?
>> We've had to build our topside
infrastructure in stages. Our engineers
keep being chased off by one danger or
another.
>> Reports about Stella Montis keep coming
in and it's unlike anything we've seen
before. continue.
>> There may be records or relics from the
past in there. And if so, one of the
returning raiders mentioned breaking
open an oddlooking contain.
>> All right.
No one has been killing me. So I think I
can go with a good load out this time
now.
No one has been killing me, so I'll just
go with a good load out.
>> That should heal you right up or perk
you right up. Honestly, I didn't pay
attention to what you bought.
>> A wise purchase, says me.
Uh,
heat.
Yeah, I do that.
I need a blueprint for this now.
All right, this should be enough.
Oh, this is stellamon is night raid too.
Yeah, just don't die, Jock. That's all I
wish. I just don't wish to die.
They'll loot every nook and corner.
Okay,
we will literally loot every nook and
corner and
get that goop.
Yep.
Oh, wait. My my jaw got dislocated.
There was something. What the heck? What
the heck? What the heck?
I just opened my mouth wide and it just
stuck there for 3 seconds. Ah,
it was hurting.
N
This is Shaunie. You're looking for
shipping containers labeled J Cosma.
That's all the help I can offer.
Okay.
Don't shoot.
>> Don't shoot.
Bro, it feels different.
Okay, we need good stuff.
Hey,
All right, this guy looted every single
thing while I was fighting.
Oh [\h__\h]
[groaning]
Come on.
>> Don't shoot.
Okay.
Got nothing here.
Use
that metro entrance.
>> Okay.
Oh my god. Are they upstairs?
I didn't get any goop, man.
I want gooper.
I need more goo.
Oh my god. Oh my god. We extracting now.
We got one of them. Let's go.
I needed that.
Uh,
>> go to the seat vault.
>> We can go to the seal though. That's
high loot there, you know.
There's a raider hatch uh over there.
Oh yeah. What's this?
Nothing much.
Don't shoot.
>> Who is this guy talking?
Oh my god.
Oh, somebody already loot. Look at all
of this.
Wow.
People
already looted this
I need a lot of senses.
Don't shoot.
>> All right.
>> There's nothing here.
>> Where are you?
People
got all the loot from here. Crazy.
Every single one of them is looted.
Not
as love.
Oh,
wait. These are not loaded.
There's nothing
Are these looted?
Feels like it's all of these are looted.
Oh god, there's PvP players.
Welcome.
Oh my god.
>> Thank you.
Hello bread.
We got the power road finally.
Someone gave us this blueprint,
which is nice.
Compensator.
Stella is actually good now.
And this recycle 10k. Nice.
I have to get to 5 million.
I have to get to 5 million though. Oh my
god. I'm still in I'm still in greens
and blues. I need a No, not greens. I'm
still in whites and greens
as you see only rarely blues. Should I
start PvPing? But if I PvP I'll lose
this peaceful
coming to the map and looting
everything. That kind of vibe. No,
cuz it's aggression behavior based
matchmaking.
People will steal my stuff.
Maybe I'll hit 5K by January and then
I'll PVP cuz I don't need to worry about
much stuff now. I can sell everything,
right?
So, if if I were to count how much do I
have
in total? Let's see
if I had to sell all of these.
Yeah, these are like no nothing.
I need actual guns.
And we need to get the purple looting
argument as well. Yep, that is
important.
Oh my god, there's so much
I don't think it will. It's It probably
going to be like 3 thou 300,000 or
something or less.
649.
Yeah. Too low.
Control for Yeah, I am doing that.
Yeah, I'm doing that. You can't Yeah,
holding control and this is how you do.
You can't like hold and like click over
here. It will not select everything till
here. Nope.
Okay. Skill point
increases maximum weight you can carry.
There's a chance to relate twice as many
items.
Ei
critical hit your stamina.
I want to get this man.
Uh,
okay. Right.
I had an image. I could have followed it
on how to
like the skill tree stuff there.
Yeah, you got a more to unlock. Nice.
Okay, one second.
Oh my god.
Pictures. My stream will be lagging. I
just open browser.
I just got Thank you for the reminder.
I'll just drink water.
Nothing.
Okay. Looting argument. I need to get
that.
Uh,
okay.
>> Close this.
>> How can I get pink color? What color?
Pink color. I think you can change your
color on Twitch.
Can change your color on Twitch.
Username color.
Should I go with the blue argument and
get like get a lot of loot?
But thing is everyone is looting so
quickly.
Why
people be so quick? Oh,
wow. So, what amount of followers
consider good on Twitch? I'm not sure.
That's a question I wouldn't know an
answer to.
points.
Yeah, the channel points. Those are
called channel points. You can redeem
stuff and everything.
Stella.
Hi. Hi, D.
Let's go.
I'm noticing that my PC is able to
handle this if I'm not a uh opening my
browser.
Okay.
Technology got Okay.
Oh my god.
>> Toledo is asleep.
>> Okay, we have to extract.
>> Oh my god. Vigilant after sunset.
>> Bro,
did you see that? Two blueprints.
No, one blueprint and two purple.
Oh my god,
bro. [laughter]
I'm rich.
I am rich and I
No way.
It was worth it.
I don't have it.
I need three senses, huh?
Yeah, I have to extract, man. I should
not die.
Oh my lord. Holy made it.
Oh, nice. Oh. Oh.
Oh my god.
We rich, Dio.
Nice, nice, nice.
Any plans for XMAS? I know.
I actually don't have any plans at all,
man.
Oh, honestly speaking, I do not have any
plans.
I'm just going to stream.
Oh, I have exams now.
I have exams.
Where was I?
Um I don't have much friends to go for
party or club and stuff.
So that that's a thing.
Oh my lord. Stop. Don't give me this
sweat.
You're making me seriously freaking out.
>> Okay, we have to extract.
>> Take that entrance.
>> Don't shoot.
Oh my lord. Holy god, this fireball.
Okay.
Okay, I think Stella Montus is the best
way to get
Tons of money.
I honestly feel like it
saying I don't need it.
Hey, don't shoot.
Hello, Raider.
I'm I'm scared of this guy.
Oh, there's a stitcher.
Where am I?
Heat. Heat.
Holy Mary, mother of God.
>> Team up.
Don't shoot.
Hey, team up.
Hey, don't shoot.
All right.
>> Hello.
What did he say? What did he say?
What did he just say?
Heat. Heat.
Don't shoot.
>> Hello.
>> Hey there.
>> Oh my lord. Holy m
nice blueprint.
Oh, gyro. Gro guy.
>> Hey, team up.
Hey, want to team up?
>> Okay,
>> don't shoot.
Thanks.
>> What was that guy saying?
Okay.
Oh my god. Look at this.
Crazy.
Crazy,
bro.
That one. This is the It's the It's the
key.
Oh my god. The amount of
the amount of
the amount of stuff is crazy.
Expedition. What happened? Yeah,
there you go. Oh, you got your stuff. N
humidifier. I need a humidifier.
Six.
Gas mine.
Um.
There's a monster cave.
Hello Solar.
Uh,
we didn't think
I'm saving the other stuff
for now.
But yeah, I need leaper core. No,
leaper. We need leaper. Uh,
I need to get leaper.
Or we can just choose Stella again.
Yeah, we can just do Stella. Yeah, we
can just do Stella.
We need more loot now.
So, it's better I get more loot.
I have to get to 5 million. So, yeah.
Uh
Stitcher,
I got our shields are not running out.
That's good to see
bandages.
Oh, this thing
one horrible. Yeah, two. Okay, we we are
good.
This should be enough, I guess.
Oh, wait. It's normal. Stella,
I thought it's night. Yeah, night. We
need night. We need the bulk blueprints.
The thing is I need to know where I have
to go. That if I know where's the good
place to go loot, I have to go run there
and
get it before other people loot.
I mean I mean if it if I if my behavior
was aggressive. No, if other people have
looted an area, I can just go kill them
and get their loot. But that's also
risky.
Oh, what is the sound?
Don't shoot.
Hey, Apollo here. Listen, did you bring
those grenades, Raider? My new designs
look great on paper, but I'll need
someone to chuck them at some machines
to know anything for sure.
Okay, I need to do parkour. No. Okay,
this is a uh this is a fresh rate. Okay,
this is a fresh rate.
Oh my lord. Don't die.
I have to get up here.
[groaning]
How will I join? Go ahead.
We should make a game one day. No, I
gave up on that dream.
Oh my lord. No.
It is too much for one person to do
everything.
I wasted so many bullets.
>> Don't shoot.
How do I get up there?
>> Thanks.
Don't shoot.
Oh my god.
How do I get up there?
I'm wasting my time.
Oh, battery. I needed this.
Oh, wow. Nice.
Okay, let's go loot. This is
Uh, this is just dumb.
>> Go to medical research.
There's nothing here.
It's full looted. Fully looted. Oh god.
>> Don't shoot.
>> What the heck? [groaning]
Avi light shield.
Did someone die?
Let's go to medical research.
Everyone looted and left.
Meanwhile, there's me.
Stop alerting where I am.
Everyone looted this area.
Have you reached your goal? What goal?
What goal?
Uh oh, that one. Nope. Nope, I haven't.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Assembly line.
Wish I could help. No worries. It's
fine. It's a huge amount. It's all good.
You don't need to
It seems everyone took the load from
this area.
Interesting.
>> Head home at the lobby Metro.
Live evidence fixed. So I fixed it
myself.
That must have been a good experience.
Like it will be hard, but hope you had a
had fun.
Hope you had fun learning how to fix and
everything.
Someone died here.
Why did he give up?
Don't shoot.
Don't shoot to
Replace the fuse in my fridges plus the
new stuff. Oh, that's nice.
>> Don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
Oh my god, almost died.
>> Head home at the loading bay metro.
>> I don't have enough
Let's use that metro entrance.
Oh, nice goop.
Yes. Yes.
Okay, we extracting
my back is bad pythons. I told him to
pay.
Oh.
We got rusted gear finally.
The last one riding his pers dry.
[laughter]
Train arrives. Doors opening shortly.
Standby.
Okay.
steep yet still pays the same price or
higher.
O,
that means you're skilled. You can like
fix stuff and everything. That's really
nice.
That is really nice.
The thought of all that potential
knowledge, baby.
>> I've been pestering Tanwen for a while
now.
>> Oh, lure grenade.
>> Her customer service is questionable,
but she's a wizard with a wrench.
All of Sparanza is buzzing about Stella
Montis right now, and I admit it's
caught my attention. Have a look around.
>> Magneto,
>> if you see anything significant that you
can't bring back, take a photo. Oh, and
bring me back some new things if you
find any.
>> Blow a controller.
I am danger because I hold my tongue
back. I'll just say stuff on this.
Oh, I see.
Oh, my stash is full. Oh my lord.
24.
Okay, we need to sell some stuff which
we don't need.
Okay, we don't need this.
Has been up since 2:00 a.m. Yeah, but
crazy.
Oh, yeah. It's the No, it's not the
weekends. Wait. Oh, yeah. It's
Christmas holidays. So
[music]
yeah, it's night for me. 8:00 p.m. It's
on the stream the time. Go to bed. I
sleep at 5:00 a.m. What do you mean?
I sleep late though.
Nowadays, I've been sleeping late
actually.
I'll tell you what I do. I watch Aso or
Straoud or other streamers like at 2:00
a.m. or 1:00 a.m. cuz they get online by
that time cuz of time zone.
Um, I feel bored. I feel not sleepy. So,
I just watch them. Maybe play some
games.
And what else?
Yeah.
And then the usual.
Then by 8 or 7:30 or 6:30 a.m., Peanut
gets uh he starts streaming. to watch
him [laughter] cuz he's been playing
this game. That's why I've been
uh watching him nowadays
on Twitch.
I go
Where to find this restaurant?
I feel
like
blue game.
Wait, Fuzzy. Wait, I didn't see that.
That was a Twitch streamer.
Whose key has okay
on a paint bottle? Oh my god. Apply some
band-aid please to apply
some bandit.
Apollo speaking. Gate still standing.
Raider, you'll find the unfinished
structures scattered around the valley.
Look for construction signs and cones.
My previous crew came under heavy fire
before they could finish up.
Oh, it's a Japanese streamer YouTuber.
I'll just follow him.
Oh, never mind.
How did a pain bottle just cut your
finger? I didn't get that. What? What?
Ah, the tin can. Oh, it might be the tin
can being sharp. Ah,
well, sometimes it happens, I guess.
Let's go to the Pilgrim's Peak.
Oh [\h__\h]
[snorts]
There's people here.
I start looting.
What's your favorite movie?
I actually don't know. I mean,
Hello there.
>> I don't actually know.
Hey there.
>> Favorite game.
H I have a lot of favorites.
I had a lot of favorites. Yeah, like
Fortnite was one of them. Then this game
is nice. I love it.
is a bit different and fun. Also fun.
First time playing an extraction shooter
and it's actually amazing.
I'll pretend I'm a new player and he'll
let me go first.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. That's a bobcat. That's a
bobcat.
Oh my god.
How was
Yeah. Uh favorite games? Yeah. Fortnite
FPS genre games are really fun. I enjoy
it. Love it.
I enjoy it. Love it. Um,
>> let's go to the warehouse
>> then.
How much is this worth?
Oh [\h__\h] Go go go go go go. Run, run,
run, run.
What?
Fudge. Fudge. Fudge. Fudge. Fudge.
Don't start. Don't start. Don't start.
Oh. No.
No. My Bobcat. My Bobcat.
The stupid rocketeer mancraft
I have watched firecraft stuff.
It's really nice.
I have to think about other types of
contents. Reaction content. I'm not good
at it.
>> Honestly, I'm not good at reaction
content.
Okay. Make it. Make it. Make it. Make
it. Make it. I'm going to die. I'm going
to die. I'm going to die. I'm going to
die.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god. One HP clutch podcast. I have
done podcast before. It didn't go well.
I'm not a good M uh host.
But I have to really figure out my
stuff, man.
It's more like I I am afraid of trying
out new stuff, I guess.
Not sure.
I could try experimenting with stuff.
That is fine.
I don't know. I tried it. Yeah, I'll try
it someday.
Oh yeah. How many hours did I spend in
this game? I want to see.
22 hours.
Let me check my Steam.
Oh, 42 hours. 42.6 hours. Crazy.
[snorts]
Who is the highest? Oh, 90.
153.
153. You're buck.
What is this launch tower loot? I want
to see this.
Let's play this also. What is this?
Okay, let's go.
Launch tower loot. What is that?
>> Do we land somewhere? What is happening?
M.
I just sit down and grind. I guess this
game, not grind, like casually just play
play.
What?
Go to the launch towers.
>> Okay, launch tower as well.
>> Just a gentle reminder to keep an eye
out for those salvage sites for TN. It
may be just what we need to get her to
pull her weight.
You have a bigger attention span than
me. Attention. What is attention span
again?
ability to multitask or focusing on only
one thing at a time. What is it?
I completely forgot
one thing at a time. Oh,
[clears throat]
I think so. I I'm not sure though.
All
right, let's go.
Not sure how I will reach there but
playing solo is a bit
you're focusing on objectives and trying
to get loot and extract, right? Playing
with a teammate and stuff or squad is
different.
Yeah,
because you have to have a team
communication,
all that stuff, which is really nice to
be honest.
But now I would have going to a
different game, but your commentary has
made me stay. Otherwise, I need someone
to talk to.
I honestly feel like
my commentary is a bit bland.
Not sure.
But yeah, I've always felt like my
commentary has been bland. I need to
work on all these stuff.
I really, don't worry, I also have it.
Don't worry, I also have it.
Did someone die?
>> Don't shoot.
I like painting. Ah,
ending is nice.
Eding is really nice.
Hello there.
>> Hey
Oh, he came for the mushrooms. Oh,
that's why he just surrendered.
Poor guy.
Yeah, go ahead.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Tell me your suggestion.
Feel free to suggest games.
>> Hello.
>> Don't shoot. Hey.
I got 10 of it. No.
Hello, penguin soldier.
Welcome. Welcome. Hello. Hello.
Hola,
did you come by on my last stream? I
think I was not able to read kick chat.
So I for completely forgot that I was
streaming on kick. So I really apologize
for that.
I believe it was you or someone else. I
forgot.
But there's a lot of ads on YouTube. Oh
my god.
Melon Sandbox. I think
I've heard of that game. I have to try
it out.
Last fighting.
Did two people die?
What?
And who's the new moderators? I have no
moderators at the moment. I'll only add
like rece moderators
when I feel like there's a need for it.
So far, I'm solo managing it.
Can climb up the tower. I think you can
climb up the tower.
Yeah, you can climb up the tower.
But where is it?
[panting]
But how do I
use a play?
Wait, how do I
agent?
Hey. Hello.
There you go.
>> [snorts]
>> No.
Ah, could you help me? I died.
Please help.
Please,
[laughter]
I don't have it.
Hey guys. Guys,
please
don't
bro.
>> Hey, sorry.
[laughter]
>> I got clapped. Yep.
Well, it is what it is.
Ah, what do you mean this? Uh, it's two
those three fireball uh thingy came. No,
one fireball and three balls.
O,
I forgot. What did I even have?
I didn't get any much loot now. I Oh, I
lost my blue kit.
Evil laugh.
Yep. Nothing.
Progress. Oh, my progression lost.
That's okay.
>> Henburger
Matriarch is here. No, no, no. Matriarch
is not here.
Ah,
it's applied of requested.
We go that
>> [laughter]
>> receding hair life.
Yeah,
I will get that. Yeah.
Are you streaming on Twitch? I'm
streaming on YouTube, Twitch, and Kick
MB.
Oh, speaking of which, I'm not even
looking at beam chat now. The my
multistream
applications don't even show the beam
chat. I have to keep it as a browser
source or something. O
>> Oh, yeah. I completely forgot about
that.
Time
humidifier. I need a fine humidifier.
Could be here or
in parade city.
No, wait. Bluegate it will have it in
the near village.
When are you hiring mods? Um, probably
now. Not now. Like in the few far
future. Not now though.
Yeah. Not now. In my current size,
I can handle it myself, I guess.
Yeah.
Wait, it's 9, right? Should I wrap up?
What time? How many hours are we
streaming today?
Three. Just three.
Wow. Today.
Wow.
So, the thing is that a part of me wants
to continue, but a part of me is like I
should take a rest cuz I've been playing
from the morning like 6:00 a.m.
onwards.
Oh, wait a new chicken. What? It's
white.
Oh. Oh, new items.
Oh, new items.
>> Oh, that is new, I think.
Please stop reading.
>> Okay.
Beachside
both hook.
>> [laughter]
>> A picnic basket. That's nice.
Oh, you can like you can like you can
like um
Oh, you can go with a darker color and
like
Oh,
Crazy.
Damn,
this is a crazy one. [laughter]
A ritual staff.
Cornelio.
I wanted this black chicken
rooster.
Oh, this is also nice.
Did you get my comment? Go to sleep.
Also, jog being awake at 9:00 p.m.
later. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I did see the
comment.
>> Did I know Russ Paul?
Like,
never mind. Yeah, it's okay. Uh,
we can close.
Yeah, I will wrap it up. I feel like I'm
being sleepy. I don't want to uh stream
with low energy. Yep. Nope. Nope.
Uh expiration wise, let's see.
Uh okay. Winter uh Christmas event like
the winter event. We are done with that.
Expedition wise, we need a little bit of
humidifiers and leaper.
Yeah, we got to start killing these
arcs.
Big bosses.
I got to start killing them.
I won't be sleep. I won't sleep though.
Solar.
I won't sleep. I'll just be on my phone
or just either steady or um watch videos
or just hang or chill.
Yeah.
Leader board. Who's number one
currently?
Lilac.
Wow.
Oh, look. That's me.
2x promotion.
So, there's five days left. I'll I'll
I'll do this later. I think I I think I
feel like I can finish this off.
I just need to get three star.
This is another thing. Yeah. Yeah.
Harvesting uh
we can also
co snap event is best leaper. Yeah, this
guy we got to kill this leaper.
Probably I'll try uh queuing up with
randoms and see how that goes.
Yeah, this is new. Okay.
Hi. Anyway, we will wrap it up here.
How to exit the game from
Oh, you can't.
>> Oh, there. There you go. You can.
Hi. Uh,
okay. We will wrap it up over here
everyone. Thank you for watching.
Thank you for coming by.
It was really fun.
I enjoy my time playing the game.
We uh got two skill points.
We reached level 37 or something. Not
37. Around 30 plus.
Yeah, around the line of 30 to 35 or
something. Yeah, 31. I don't know.
And uh what else? We got a lot of
blueprints today. We got a lot of good
loot from Stellar. That's nice. Yeah, if
we keep going like this, I probably
think I will get my first million. Well,
level 33. Oh, okay. Nice. Level 33.
Yeah, I should try to get my first
million and then I should like
um
keep on looting, looting, looting and um
after that I will try more PvP stuff. I
want to get I know I'm like getting
afraid of fights and stuff. I have to
It's an extraction shooter so I have to
keep on learning how to play the game
and be more braver.
Yeah, that is a thing. I have to do that
too.
I think if I'm queuing up probably with
Bacon, I have to help him with his quest
and everything. He's also
new to the game, right?
And he's also figuring things out.
So, yeah. Uh yeah, I'll
see how this journey with Arc Raiders
goes. It's really a fun game and
enjoying this game a lot.
I watching this game uh for a while and
finally I'm able to play it and it's
fun. It is fun.
Not too gr Yeah, a little bit grindy,
but it is an extraction shooter. Like
once you do the expedition, your
character will be fully reseted. You
have to do everything all of the
everything again.
All right.
>> [laughter]
>> So yeah, it is a bit gritty, but yeah,
for casual playing it is fun. I can if I
ever want to, I can just casually come
in and stuff. I don't have to force
myself to play the game. No, that's the
difference. Unlike those gacha games.
Yeah, [laughter]
that's a different story. All together,
right? Anyone
I shall go to sleep. Thank you all for
today. Hope you enjoy today. What's the
joke?
And before I leave, I'll redirect you to
my always on channel.
YouTube is good. It's just Twitch. I
need a raid.
I was wondering if I should make a
always channel on kick.
Uh not sure.
Jo next 2.7
read. Okay. For those who are watching
on YouTube, you will be redirected to my
24x7 channel. For those who are on
Twitch, you'll also Yeah. You Yeah. Uh
for YouTube it will be my V channel. For
Twitch you you will be rate rated to the
24x7 channel. Hi.
Hi. Hi.
They're waiting. Hi.
Uh, before I switch, yesterday I
realized that my the stream was not
streaming.
The stream was not streaming. Yesterday
uh wait.
Yeah, yesterday the stream was not
streaming. Yeah, it is working. Hi. The
bit rate is a bit low cuz I was
currently right now streaming. Yeah. Hi.
3 2 1. Thank you for watching and have a
good one you guys.
Bye-bye. Good night. Good night.
Have a good one.